wepc.com 2011-07-08

# WePC

The web site WePC.com ("Site") is a joint website of Intel Corporation ("Intel") and ASUSTek Computer Incorporated ("ASUS"), who are committed to protecting the privacy of information you provide to this site. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Site and governs collection and usage of personal data through this Site. This Statement of Privacy does not apply to other ASUS or Intel sites, products, or services. 

By using this Site, you consent to the collection and use of the information and data as described here. If we decide to change this privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you will always know what information we collect, and how we use it. 

**Collection and Use of Personal Data:** On the Site, we only store personal information relating to you with your permission. You may choose to reveal information to us if, for example, you register for a service, enter a contest or complete a survey. If you choose to register for an activity on the Site, you may be asked for your formal consent regarding collection and usage of your personally identifiable information. Unless otherwise stated when you register, the personal information collected on this Site will be used to operate the Site and to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized. 

ASUS and Intel will share personal information with one another once collected from you through the Site. Once shared, ASUS and Intel will only use your personal information in accordance with the respective Privacy Policies of each company. 

You may view Intel's Privacy Policy here:   
[http://www.intel.com/sites/corporate/privacy.htm?iid=HMPAGE+Footer_privacy](http://www.intel.com/sites/corporate/privacy.htm)  

You may view ASUS' Privacy Policy here: [http://usa.asus.com/privacy.aspx](http://usa.asus.com/privacy.aspx)  

Third parties such as Communications Blueprint (ComBlu) who assist ASUS and Intel in the management of the Site may access and collect information on behalf of ASUS or Intel through the Site, but they are not allowed to use this data for their own business purposes separate from their relationship with ASUS or Intel. We will only share your personal data with these third parties according to applicable data protection laws or with your express permission. This data is used by these third parties solely for the purposes described under this Privacy Statement. 

ASUS and Intel will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so or in line with applicable laws. 

**Access to Your Personal Information:** You can review and edit the personal information you provided at this Site by logging in and changing your information. 

**Links to Other Sites:** This site contains links to other sites. ASUS and Intel are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of third party Web sites you may access through the Site. 

**Inquiries:** If you have any questions about this privacy statement -- if, for example, you wish to inspect or update the information we hold about you -- please _Contact Us_.
